Now, let's talk about Link at last.
The list contains a consist of a number of darts in which each none has in next pointer to the following
element.
The length of the last nod is there and the list is null, which indicates the end of the list.
This is very important and think about it not inside the link.
At least that consists of not like a two separate that two separate boxes, the one that contains data
and the other that contains a reference to the next.
Not OK.
So in order to create a link, at least in C, we start by struct nod and inside the node.
We inside the node structure we have int data variable called data and struck node and the pointer for
the next note.
This is the reference, so the first one is making an end data that stores the data of an integer and
int linked list and struck note that contains a reference to the next node and this link at list to
it to create a linkage list or sorry.
It would create a none for the linkage list in Java.
We start by public last list note and we start by making private and data and private lists, not the
next and we, the constructor and getters and setters.
Later on in the end, examples and exercises, we are going to construct this link at least from zero.
So.
The linked list and see, we have created it before the struck note and very important note that in
sea there is no class, so we use the struct structure.
We are creating a new data structure called node, and this node contains data and struck notes that
point to for the next.
And we create a structure A. We have three nodes the head, the middle and the last.
We start by creating had equal malak.
We are reserving memory allocation the size for the struct node.
So when we call that malloc, we are reserving the memory and we are creating a structure inside this
memory middle had and last.
OK.
Now, in order to assign the variables.
And the data to the variables or to their nodes, so we put had this flash, so dash and this this angle,
this diamond data equal to 18, so this line will give us 18 to the head.
So you see guys here, we have three nods.
We have created three nodes head, middle and last.
And these numbers like 1024 2024 and three thousand forty.
Are there indices that are that addresses inside that memory?
So don't worry about them.
We are.
We are interested in understanding.
That the memory inside the mirror, in order to create the nods, we have to use Malak and in order
to insert data inside these nodes we use had Dash this flash and we put data equal to 18.
We are inserting inside.
We are associating and instantiating that data valuable to 18 in hard data variable, 66 in the middle
and the data variable equal to one one nine in the last.
Not OK.
No, they're very important thing that we should take care, that it is a linked list so we are not
making.
These nodes are like separate notes.
We need to link them how to link them.
We need to associate and tell every node what its next.
So we are telling head, we are accessing that the head and the next pointer to it would be the middle
and the next to the middle would be the last.
OK.
And the last would be the No.
So this association will tell us how to create the ending at less OK in the next video.
We are going to talk about printing the link.